Madly Madagascar is a animation, comedy, family film directed by David Soren.
Your favorite Madagascar pals are back in an all-new adventure!
Alex's favorite holiday, Valentine's Day, brings hilarious
surprises and excitement for the entire gang.
Melman plans a big surprise for Gloria, Marty tries to impress a new friend and
everyone wants to get their hands on King Julien's love potion.
You'll fall in LOVE with Madly Madagascar!
Alex (voice), played by Ben Stiller.
Marty (voice), played by Chris Rock.
Melman (voice), played by David Schwimmer.
Gloria (voice), played by Jada Pinkett Smith.
Maurice (voice), played by Cedric the Entertainer.
Mort (voice), played by Andy Richter.
Madagascar is a media franchise owned and produced by DreamWorks Animation.
The voices of Ben Stiller, Chris Rock, David Schwimmer and
Jada Pinkett Smith are featured in the films.
It began with the 2005 film Madagascar, followed by Escape 2
Africa in 2008 and Europe's Most Wanted in 2012.
A spin-off film featuring the penguins, titled Penguins
of Madagascar, was released in 2014.
A fourth main film, Madagascar 4, was announced for 2018, but has since been removed
from its schedule indefinitely due to the studio's restructuring in 2015.
The overall plot through the series follows the adventures of four anthropomorphic Central Park Zoo animals who have spent their
lives in blissful captivity and are unexpectedly shipped back to Kenya initially, but are shipwrecked on Madagascar.
Now they must struggle to survive while attempting to return to New York City with the help of a
crafty cadre of Adélie penguins and with many other characters along the way.
The franchise's films have received mixed-to-positive critical reviews.
The film explores themes of holiday, africa, lion, hippopotamus, giraffe.
The tone is lighthearted.